<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_RU_SCENARIOS_EA">

        <LanguageRef>LANG_RU</LanguageRef>

        <Contributors>
            <Name>GNERWA LANG</Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>
            <!-- GENERAL OBJECTIVE(s)-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_GENERAL_SKIRMISH</LocID>                                   <Text>Устраните всех противников!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!--_______________CONFLUENCE__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>EA_CONFLUENCE_ID</LocID>                                              <Text>Слияние</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>        <LocID>EA_CONFLUENCE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                     <Text><![CDATA[Энергетические поля разделяют землю на три изолированных региона. <b>Главнокомандующий Суверенов</b> в джунглях пытается выжать из территории всё до последней капли, в то время как <b>Дети Источника</b> в пустыне не могут терпеть осквернения своих древних мест покоя. А <b>лидер Фоссориан</b> просто хочет испытать новое оружие на всех, кто окажется в пределах досягаемости!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CONFLUENCE_INTRO</LocID>                                           <Text>Древний обвал гигантской терраформирующей башни разделил территорию на три отдельных региона. Вытекшая проводящая жидкость образовала непроходимое слияние. Несколько древних мостов, соединяющих берега, недавно активировались, и вновь открывшиеся пути привели колонии на противоположных берегах к прямому конфликту.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CONFLUENCE_VICTORY</LocID>                                         <Text>Victory! The whole territory is unified! The success of your colonies may even attract the attention of the Temple City Alliance and you will finally gain the well-deserved protection and trade roads connection. However, in the confusion of the clash, one question remains unanswered. Who built the bridges that now connect the regions? Who else could profit from this bloody clash?</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER</LocID>                                    <Text>Greetings, commander. I am with the Keepers Guild. I have a well-paying job for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_COMANDER</LocID>                                  <Text>I'm listening.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER1</LocID>                                   <Text>Not far from here, there's a slave camp. The chief slaver has been a thorn in my side for some time. If you burn it down, I'll give you one Fusion Core.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER2</LocID>                                   <Text>Now, return for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER3</LocID>                                   <Text>I have no more tasks for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
          
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER_NOT_DONE</LocID>                           <Text>Burn down the slave camp first. Then you'll receive your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER_DONE</LocID>                               <Text>Thank you. Here is your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
 
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_CONFLUENCE_KEEPER</LocID>                                  <Text>Burn down the slave camp!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            
            <!--_____________AWAIT_______________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_AWAIT_ID</LocID>                                                  <Text>Долина Ожидания</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_AWAIT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                         <Text><![CDATA[Приготовьте защиту, прежде чем мощный враг достигнет вашей базы!\n\nНравится жанр Защита Башен? Попробуйте <b>"оборону" Фоссорианами</b>!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_AWAIT_INTRO</LocID>                                               <Text>Признаем, мы знали, что эти мерзкие Кибержуки рано или поздно напомнят о себе, если мы начнем строить поселение на их границах. Но никто не ожидал Инквизиции! Ребята, построившие базу на западе, замолчали пару циклов назад. Давайте проверим там. Может, они оставили что-то для укрепления нашей обороны!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_AWAIT_VICTORY</LocID>                                             <Text>We must have stumbled onto something big! Maybe one of the artifacts we've discovered in the Primal ruins is really valued by those stupid Cyberbugs. Anyway, our position is too strong for them now. They will not dare to send any more of their precious inquisitors to die!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_AWAIT_KEEPER</LocID>                                         <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. I don't have any tasks for you. Since a formidable enemy is approaching and you must be short of time, I'll give you some information instead.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_AWAIT_KEEPER1</LocID>                                        <Text>Here, you will find a teleport that will take you to a distant island where you can obtain rare items and strengthen yourself before the upcoming battle.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_AWAIT_KEEPER2</LocID>                                        <Text>I'm afraid I can't do more for you, but I'm keeping my fingers crossed.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_AWAIT_KEEPER4</LocID>                                        <Text>Unfortunately, I can't help you any further.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <!--_________________GOLD FEVER_______________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_GOLD_FEVER_ID</LocID>                                             <Text>Золотая лихорадка</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_GOLD_FEVER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                    <Text><![CDATA[Золотая лихорадка охватила землю после того, как информация о богатом древнем объекте распространилась! <b>Фоссориане с юго-запада</b> ищут самый быстрый путь к центру руин. В то же время <b>Дети Источника</b> спешат с северо-востока. <b>Помните, что второе место здесь — это просто другое название для поражения!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_GOLD_FEVER_INTRO</LocID>                                          <Text>Древние руины в центральной части привлекли некоторых "тараканов". Незаконные золотодобытчики переплавляли огромное количество древних артефактов из-за высокого содержания в них золота! Теперь по всей местности разбросаны монеты Ауры! Доберитесь туда как можно быстрее, конфискуйте богатство и используйте его для того, чтобы сделать ваших предков гордыми... Или, в вашем случае, хотя бы менее стыдными.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_GOLD_FEVER_VICTORY</LocID>                                        <Text>Now that the dust has settled using all the wealth solely for military production is no longer necessary! Imagine what is possible now! Perhaps a golden statue, a luxury mansion, or a private solar yacht? And they say that wealth corrupts! Nonsense! </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER</LocID>                                    <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. I have a difficult task for you today.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER1</LocID>                                   <Text>In the surrounding area, there are two monster nests.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER2</LocID>                                   <Text>If you manage to visit and clear out both of them, I will reward you gladly and generously.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER3</LocID>                                   <Text>Now return for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
         
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER_NOT_DONE</LocID>                           <Text>You need to clear out both beast nests!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
              
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER_DONE</LocID>                               <Text>Thank you. Here is your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
                
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_GOLD_FEVER_DONE_DONE</LocID>                                 <Text>I have no more tasks for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER</LocID>                                  <Text>Clear out beast nests 0/2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER1</LocID>                                 <Text>Clear out beast nests 1/2</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_GOLD_FEVER_KEEPER2</LocID>                                 <Text>Return for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <!--_____________________ARCH_____________________________________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_EA_ARCH</LocID>                                         <Text>Арка</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_EA_ARCH_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                             <Text><![CDATA[Вступите в безжалостную дуэль между <b>Фоссорианами</b> и <b>Детьми Источника</b> на сухом и негостеприимном острове. Далекая заброшенная база может склонить чашу весов в вашу пользу.</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_EA_ARCH_INTRODUCTION</LocID>                            <Text>До Коллапса UNSS пытались контролировать здесь всё. Теперь они едва справляются с управлением собственной территории. Так что это наш шанс свести счеты с нашими "любимыми" соседями без официальных последствий. Ресурсы заброшенной базы на севере должны дать нам преимущество. Дадим им попробовать вкус наших клинков!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MAP_SCENARIO_EA_ARCH_VICTORY</LocID>                                 <Text>We've crushed them and because their colony will become a protectorate, it can hardly be labeled as genocide. Now let the UNSS committee for war crimes come! We are clean as a... What's the thing making those high-pitched noises called?</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_ARCH_KEEPER</LocID>                                          <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. I have a straightforward task for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <!-- TODO the unit name -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_ARCH_KEEPER1</LocID>                                         <Text>The thing is, I once captured a group of wild monsters called "Baloo." I wanted to tame them, but I couldn't. Instead, they multiplied, and now I don't know what to do with them. I'll open a path to them for you, and if you get rid of them for me, I will reward you generously.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_ARCH_KEEPER2</LocID>                                         <Text>Now return for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_ARCH_KEEPER_DONE</LocID>                                     <Text>Thank you. Here is your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <!-- TODO the unit name -->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_ARCH_KEEPER_NOT_DONE</LocID>                                 <Text>You must defeat the Baloo!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_ARCH_DONE_DONE</LocID>                                       <Text>I have no more tasks for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_ARCH_KEEPER</LocID>                                        <Text>Defeat the Baloo!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>


            <!--_______________CRUMBS__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRUMBS_ID</LocID>                                                 <Text>Обломки</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRUMBS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                        <Text><![CDATA[Острова, разделенные энергетическими полями, соединены древними мостами Праймалов. <b>Суверены</b> в красных джунглях жаждут новых ресурсов. <b>Дети Источника</b> на поле желтой растительности пришли, чтобы ассимилировать врагов. И, чтобы усугубить ситуацию, две разные группы <b>Фоссориан</b> уничтожают всё на своем пути.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRUMBS_INTRO</LocID>                                              <Text><![CDATA[Острова, словно крошечные крошки, соединены древними мостами. <color=SOTS_COLOR_FUSION_CORE>Ядра синтеза</color> — это ключ к мостам, но не единственный. Энергетическая система перегружена из-за слишком многих ненасытных командиров. Блок управления скоро будет переполнен, и все мосты активируются. Ничто не останется изолированным, и мосты соединят путь к гибели.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_CRUMBS_VICTORY</LocID>                                            <Text>The bridges created a path to VICTORY, and the islands were drenched in the blood of your enemies. The key was not some ancient technology but a cunning strategy to turn your enemies into puppets.</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>
   
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_10</LocID>                                            <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>10</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_9</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>9</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_8</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>8</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_7</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>7</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_6</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>6</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_5</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>5</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_4</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>4</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_3</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>3</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_2</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>2</color> cycles.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_1</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate in <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>1</color> cycle.]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_0</LocID>                                             <Text><![CDATA[<color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>WARNING!</color>\nSystem overload! Excess energy will be diverted, and all bridges will activate... <color=SOTS_COLOR_RED>NOW!</color>]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_KEEPER</LocID>                                        <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. I have a simple task for you. You must visit the four locations I've marked on the map for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_KEEPER1</LocID>                                       <Text>These are places I camped while on my journey. I lost my ceremonial ring somewhere along the way. Find it, and I will reward you generously.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
      
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_KEEPER2</LocID>                                       <Text>You haven't searched all the locations yet.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
          
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_KEEPER3</LocID>                                       <Text>I see that you've searched all the locations. I just remembered that I put it in a different mug.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_KEEPER4</LocID>                                       <Text>You've done your job. Here is you reward!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
         
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_COMMANDER</LocID>                                     <Text>No matter how hard I search, I don't see any ring here.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
     
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_CRUMBS_DONE_DONE</LocID>                                     <Text>I have no more tasks for you.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_CRUMBS_KEEPER</LocID>                                      <Text>Find the Keeper's ring.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_CRUMBS_KEEPER1</LocID>                                     <Text>Return for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

            
            <!--_______________RIFT__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_RIFT_ID</LocID>                                                   <Text>Разлом</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_RIFT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          <Text><![CDATA[Территория, разорванная на две части. Некогда плодородная земля теперь опустошена войной. <b>Фоссориане</b>, <b>Суверены</b> и две группы <b>Детей Источника</b> неизбежно столкнутся в безжалостной битве. \nЧтобы усложнить ситуацию, все начинают с баз на противоположных берегах!]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_RIFT_INTRO</LocID>                                                <Text>Дети Источника когда-то контролировали эту богатую ресурсами территорию, но в болотах образовался разлом, разделивший землю на две части. Фоссориане и Суверены воспользовались этим, захватив территории для себя. Чтобы усугубить ситуацию, Дети Источника впали в раздор и обратились друг против друга. Ситуация настолько опасна, что даже обычно бесстрашные местные существа предпочитают держаться как можно дальше от главных дорог.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_RIFT_VICTORY</LocID>                                              <Text>This is the end. Once again, only one faction rules the land, extracting all available resources. A small step towards a great victory! Or will a new rift form, causing everything to collapse like a house of cards?</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>
    
    
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_TELEPORT</LocID>                                        <Text>It looks like this teleport was one-way only.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
               
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_KEEPER</LocID>                                          <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. Before the rift formed, I ruled these lands.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_KEEPER1</LocID>                                         <Text>After the strife began, I retreated here but can still influence events from the shadows. I would like to do one last thing and help you finally resolve the entire situation.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_KEEPER2</LocID>                                         <Text>You now have a unique opportunity to switch sides. Behind me, you can see the teleporters in each warring faction's colors.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_KEEPER3</LocID>                                         <Text>The teleporter you choose will determine which side you join. If you select the same color you currently represent, you will return to your faction.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_KEEPER4</LocID>                                         <Text>Think it over carefully. You can join the side currently winning, but you will lose everything you have built so far. That's all from me! </Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
          
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_RIFT_KEEPER5</LocID>                                         <Text>Make your damn choice already. A brutal war rages below, and there's no time to waste!</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>

                
            <!--_______________TEAR__________________________-->
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_TEAR_ID</LocID>                                                   <Text>Разрыв</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_TEAR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>                                          <Text><![CDATA[Первые<b> Дети Источника</b> находятся на одной половине острова, вторые <b>Дети Источника</b> на другой!\nНекогда единая земля была разделена на архипелаг, соединенный лишь хаотичной сетью порталов. Сможете ли вы найти путь к своему врагу?]]></Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_TEAR_INTRO</LocID>                                                <Text>Флот Суверена исследовал руины древних Праймалов, когда произошла катастрофа, разорвавшая землю на части. Две фракции Детей Источника первыми прибыли после катастрофы, но лишь одна сможет взять контроль над территорией.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>EA_TEAR_VICTORY</LocID>                                              <Text>Once, a brother, now a rival, was torn to shreds, and not a single tear was shed.</Text>    </GameDBLocalizedString>
        
        
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER</LocID>                                          <Text>Greetings, commander! I am with the Keepers Guild. Before the catastrophe that tore this land to pieces, I was the caretaker here.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER1</LocID>                                         <Text>I need you to discover all the islands and, in doing so, determine how many there are. Then come back for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER2</LocID>                                         <Text>You have yet to discover all the islands. Come back after you visit them all.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
           
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER3</LocID>                                         <Text>Great! That was the last island. Now, return for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
          
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER4</LocID>                                         <Text>Seven islands—never in my wildest dreams did I imagine the catastrophe would be so devastating! Thank you so much for your help. Now, I can start with the cartographic work.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER5</LocID>                                         <Text>Here is your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>MESSAGE_TEAR_KEEPER6</LocID>                                         <Text>The islands have been counted. I don't know of anything else you could do for me.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
                
                
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_TEAR_KEEPER</LocID>                                        <Text>Find and count all the individual islands.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
            <GameDBLocalizedString>         <LocID>OBJECTIVE_TEAR_KEEPER1</LocID>                                       <Text>Return to the Keeper for your reward.</Text>  </GameDBLocalizedString>
        
        </LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
